

# **MAYANK KASHYAP**

Sales Executive

### Contact Me

- 8299104439
- mayank.kashyap1992@g mail.com

H610 Barra World Bank

Colony Kanpur ,India

### Social Profile



facebook.com/mayank.k ashyap.351

### Other Info

### Skills

I can deal with customer as well as architect and interior designer, i can deal Tiles, sanitary ware, Granite, itallian marble, luxurious bath fittings and accessories, pipe fittings and wellness products.

## Languages

Hindi, English

### About Me

My name is Mayank Kashyap. I have been living in kanpur City since my birth. I'm working as a sales executive since 2013. I've completed my graduation in 2015. Currently I'm single. I've 5 sister's. My parents have passed away so I'm living with my sister.



## Experience

### 2013 - 2016

### Verma Trading Company | Godown Incharge/ Sales Executive

In my initial days I worked in Verma Trading Company as a godown incharge but after a few months I started working as a sales executive. I worked here for almost three years.

### 2016 - 2019

### Agarwal Tiles And Granite | Senior Sales Executive

from 2016 to 2019 I worked in Agarwal Tiles & Granite as a senior sales executive. I learned a lot here, how to behave in front of clients and how to convince a client.

## 2019 - till now Rozy Granite | Senior Sales Executive And Display Incharge

Currently I'm working in Rozy granite and tiles as a sales executive and display incharge, I'm working here since 2019.

### Education

2012 - 2015 SS degree College CSJM University Kanpur

BSc

2010 - 2012 Gandhi Smarak Inter College Govind Nagar

Kanpur | Intermediate

2008 - 2010 Mohan Vidya Mandir Inter College | High

School

Mayank Kashyap